<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GarageGuruFyp-User</string>
    <string name="contact_email">bbburhankamran@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="good_bye_cars">Goodbye Car Worries, Hello Garage Guru!</string>
    <string name="find_compare_book">Find, compare, and book trusted garages with the tap of a finger. Get competitive quotes, chat with mechanics, and get your car fixed fast and fair.</string>
    <string name="competitive_offers">Get Competitive Offers</string>
    <string name="relax_garages_bid">Relax, garages will bid for your job, offering different prices and timelines. Choose the best fit for your budget and needs.</string>
    <string name="connect_clarify">Connect &amp; Clarify</string>
    <string name="chat_directly">Chat directly with mechanics to ask questions, discuss quotes, and schedule appointments. No more confusing jargon, just clear communication.</string>
    <string name="sign_up_user">Get maintenance and repair services for your vehicle</string>
    <string name="grow_your_business">Grow your business,reach new customers</string>
    <string name="approval_pending">"Welcome to GarageGuru. Your account is pending approval. You can use it once it's approved"</string>
    <string name="high_fives">"High fives! Your car just found its new best friend - GarageGuru."</string>
    <string name="not_received_code">Not received code?</string>
    <string name="resend_code">Resend Code</string>
    <string name="customer">Customer\n</string>
    <string name="garage">Garage\n</string>
    <string name="user_type">Select user type</string>
    <string name="no_customer_found_with_these_details">No Customer found with these details</string>
    <string name="no_garage_found_with_these_details">No Garage found with these details</string>
    <string name="view_all">View All</string>
    <string name="message_empty_error">Please Enter a Message!</string>
    <string name="write_your_message">Write Your Message…</string>
    <string name="new_request">New Request</string>
    <string name="all_request">All Request</string>
    <string name="empty_error">Please Fill Empty Fields!</string>
    <string name="filter">Filter</string>
    <string name="bid_amount">Bid Amount</string>
    <string name="enter_your_bid_amount">Enter Your Bid Amount…</string>
    <string name="bid">Bid</string>
    <string name="all_bids">All Bids</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="accepted_bid">Accepted Bid</string>
    <string name="my_request">My Requests</string>
    <string name="request">Requests\n</string>
    <string name="inbox">Inbox</string>
    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="requested">Requested</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="garage_detail">Garage Detail</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="contact_detail">Contact Details</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="chat_now">Chat Now</string>
    <string name="garages">Garages</string>
    <string name="about_us">GarageGuru is a user-friendly Android application designed to revolutionize the way car owners connect with garages and seek assistance for their automotive needs. Our app aims to provide a seamless experience for both car owners and garages, creating a reliable platform for efficient and convenient car maintenance and repair services.
With GarageGuru, car owners can easily find a comprehensive list of garages in their area. These garages are verified and enlisted on the app, ensuring high-quality services. Garages have the option to pay for listing their services, enabling them to showcase their expertise and attract potential customers.
When car owners encounter a problem with their vehicle, they can post the specific issue on GarageGuru. Garages registered on the app will then have the ability to view and approach the users with fair and competitive repair quotes. Users can make an informed decision by considering ratings, location, and price offers from the garages. This empowers car owners to choose the best-suited garage for their needs, ensuring quality repairs and peace of mind.
Additionally, GarageGuru offers a convenient pickup feature. In situations where a user is involved in an accident or finds themselves stranded in a location without nearby garages, they can rely on the app to locate and contact the nearest garage for assistance. This feature ensures prompt response and support during critical times, enhancing user safety and convenience.
</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="share_app">Share App</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="about_us_title">About Us</string>
    <string name="app_version">App Version</string>
>>>>>>> Stashed changes
</resources>